RYAN WARD

Fourth Year Electrical and Computer Engineering Student ryan.ward17@outlook.com · LinkedIn · 0403220572

Going into my fourth year at the University of Queensland studying a combined Bachelors/Masters of Electrical and Computer engineering, my goal is to gain experience in the industry whilst studying and working. I am proficient in software development, am an efficient problem solver and a proven fast learner. Through my part time jobs with BHP, AutoCare and Centric Technologies, I have developed excellent communication and people skills, and have experienced working in a mature environment.

EXPERIENCE

2021 - PRESENT

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, CENTRIC TECHNOLOGIES/AGFI LABS

Developing decentralized applications on the Ethereum network, in addition to agricultural tracing through blockchain technology.

2021-2022

SUPPORT WORKER, BHP

Employed to assist with the uploading of COVID-19 vaccinations into the BHP system, as well as certificate verification and support.

2016-2021

SHIFT MANAGER, PIZZA CAPERS

Shift manager and driver, was in charge of managing both day and night shifts.

2019-2020

TOYOTA BUILDER, AUTOCARE SERVICES

Working in a team of Toyota builders to prepare vehicles for the Australian roads.

EDUCATION

2019 - PRESENT

BACHELOR/MASTERS ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING,

UNIVERSITY OF QUEENSLAND

Studying Electrical and Computer engineering, with many electives focused around software and cyber-security, expected to graduate in 2023.

2011-2018

HIGH SCHOOL, IONA COLLEGE

SKILLS

- Software Development
- Computer Networks
- Electrical Design
- Solidity Development
- Smart Contract design and testing
- Fast learner
- Efficient problem solver
- Certificate III in Logistics
- Linux Operating System
- Decentralised Finance Systems

ACTIVITIES

- 2014-2021 Iona College Basketball Coach
- 2019 UQ EAIT Scholar
- 2019-2020 Team Leader for various university projects
- 2018 College House Captain and Prefect
- 2016-2018 Junior/Senior Link Tutoring

REFEREES

Available upon request.